inklineglobal.com 2018-05-14

# inKline Global, Inc

inKline Global, Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. To make your shopping experience more convenient, we must sometimes ask you for information. We maintain the privacy of your information using security technologies and adhering to policies that prevent unauthorized use of any personal information you provide. 

**What we collect and how we use information  
**To process your order, we need to know your name, email address, and mailing address. We also need your credit card number and its expiration date. 

In addition to the information that we collected from you, we will also track the use of our website. We monitor viewing and traffic patterns, customer behavior, and other similar information. We compile this information into a statistical aggregate. 

Your personal information such as email & postal address will be used internal business and administrative purposes such as to notify you of special offers, new products, services, promotions, and other similar information. 

**What we disclose to outside parties  
**We will not sell, rent or lease your personally identifiable information to others. Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we will only share the personal data you provide online with inKline Global and/or business partners who are acting on their behalf.

We do provide aggregate information about site usage and traffic patterns, stripped of any individual identification, to third parties to comply with various reporting obligations and for business or marketing purposes.

**How we protect customer information  
**When you place orders or access your account information, we use secure server SSL technology that encrypts all your personal information before it is sent to us to prevent unauthorized access to your information. 

**Our use of computer cookies  
**inKline Global, Inc. uses a feature of your Internet browser called a "cookie" to assign a unique identification to your computer. Cookies are files that your Web browser places on your computer's hard drive. These files allow you to easily access your customer data on our site. They also save you time by tracking your order information so that you do not have to reenter this information upon every visit. inKline Global, Inc. does not and cannot use cookies to retrieve personal information about you from your computer unless you knowingly provided such information.

**Security**  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

Our site's Tell-a-Friend form allows users to introduce this site to someone else. The user must provide their email address as well as the recipient's. This information is used only in the case of transmission and to let the recipient know who sent the recommendation. This information is not used for any other purpose.   

Our site's Oligo Skin Submission form allows users to upload their skin submissions to us. The user must provide their name and email address. This is to help us to contact skin authors regarding their submissions. This information will not be rented or resold to any other parties. The IP address of submitters will be logged to prevent abuse of the submission form.   

**Choice/Opt-Out**  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.  

This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

1) Unsubscribe Link  

2) Writing To Us  
Please write your concerns to the following address: 711 S Carson City Suite 4, NV 89701

3) Call Us   
Please call our technical support at +1 (866) 612-4209 and ask for removal.

**Correct/Update information**  
This site gives our customers options for changing and modifying information previously provided. Any changes in personal information, please email: [sales@inklineglobal.com](mailto:sales@inklineglobal.com)
